Velocitex is a 3D momentum puzzle game.
You guide a candy through a machine,
using slopes, bounce, grip, braking, and timing to reach the cup.
Early rooms teach one idea at a time.
Later rooms combine rails, pressure plates, moving platforms, cannons, and magnets into harder routes.
It is a playable Windows game with candy customization,
achievements, accessibility settings, room-start saves, and Room Select.
Codex helped turn design decisions into Godot and C# code,
investigate movement and saving issues, and build repeatable tests.
GPT-5.6, used through Codex, helped reason through mechanics,
edge cases, and test coverage.
Download Velocitex for Windows, and see how far your momentum can take you.